thedieselstop.com 2007-12-10

# TheDieselStop.Com - www.thedieselstop.com

## TheDieselStop.Com Privacy Information:

TheDieselStop.Com values your privacy. To keep you informed, we have created this privacy statement that discloses our purposes and methods for online collection and use of information. This statement applies to all information collected through the Ford-Diesel.Com website and information gathered from any web pages that we host.

**Site Operator and Contact for Privacy Inquiries:**

TheDieselStop.Com  
Attention: Jason Lester  
350 Henry Street  
Abingdon, VA 24210

E-mail: webmaster@thedieselstop.com

**Types of Information Collected**

Generally, personal information is not collected from visitors to the TheDieselStop.Com website. However, in order to access certain special services, personal information is requested; those cases are described in more detail below.

**Bulletin Board Registration**

TheDieselStop.Com requires a valid e-mail address for users who want to participate in the TheDieselStop.Com support forums. This helps us try to protect our community from abusive postings and provides a verifiable point of contact should legal questions arise. At any time, you have the ability to keep your e-mail address hidden from other users by selecting that option within your user profile.

Also in the forum registration, you have the option of providing some additional information such as occupation, interests, and homepage URL. This information is made available to other bulletin board users to foster a sense of community. If you have any concerns about providing this information, simply leave the fields blank and your registration will still be processed.

**Cookies**

Certain activities on the TheDieselStop.Com website involve the use of "cookies" to facilitate your experience. This includes retention of your username and password for the forums and showing a default Topic View when you visit the forums. You have the option to turn these cookies off at any time by updating your user profile preferences. If your browser doesnÕt support cookies, or if you have cookies turned off, these preferences will not be set.

**Purchasing and/or Credit Card Information**

TheDieselStop.Com strives to maintain strict security for your private information. Our online ordering pages are secure-site enabled. We do not maintain any credit card information at TheDieselStop.Com, which means that you have to provide it each time you make a purchase, but also means that your information is controlled by you alone.

**Disclosure of Personal Information**

TheDieselStop.Com does not disclose your personally identifying information to any third parties for any purpose without your prior consent. All reasonable care is taken by staff handling personal information to ensure its security both offline and online.

We at TheDieselStop.Com also reserve the right to reveal your identity (or whatever information we know about you) in the event of a complaint or legal action arising from any message posted by you.

It is also important to be aware that when you voluntarily provide personal information (e.g., last name, address, phone number) in a posting on the bulletin board, that information is publicly available and may be used by someone in a manner unintended by you. For that reason, we discourage the offering of any personally identifying information within the message board itself.

**Advertisers**

TheDieselStop.Com uses advertising banners to help support the connectivity and hardware costs associated with running a large active website. We use [Adcycle](http://www.adcycle.com/) ad serving software to keep track of what banners are shown and when those banners are clicked. The only information retained for this process is your computer's IP address. No other personal information is stored relating to advertising.
